{
    "subject": "resource/Netviewer",
    "predicate": "property/industry",
    "object": "resource/Information_technology",
    "human_readable": "Netviewer's industry is Information technology.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7907136082649231,
            "question": "What industry does Netviewer operate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6729521155357361,
            "question": "How is technology changing the landscape of Netviewer's industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.652174711227417,
            "question": "Are there any major trends affecting Netviewer's industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5872125029563904,
            "question": "What is the future outlook for Netviewer's industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5839378833770752,
            "question": "Give an example of a company in the same industry as Netviewer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5826977491378784,
            "question": "What are some challenges facing companies in Netviewer's industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.575242817401886,
            "question": "What are some examples of successful companies in Netviewer's industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.520601212978363,
            "question": "What skills would be valuable for someone working in Netviewer's industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49622198939323425,
            "question": "How does Netviewer's industry contribute to the economy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.465149849653244,
            "question": "What types of products or services might Netviewer offer?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Netviewer's industry is Information technology.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6512_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Netviewer's industry contribute to the economy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6512_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What skills would be valuable for someone working in Netviewer's industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6512_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some examples of successful companies in Netviewer's industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6512_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6512_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6512_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6512_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6512_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6512_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6512_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6512_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6512_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6512_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6512_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Netviewer, a company operating in the software and collaboration services space. They describe its growth, strategies, technological advancements, and competitive landscape, all of which fall under the broader category of the Information Technology industry."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}